

### 07895667979

# WEB DEVELOPER

danhart21390@gmail.com

# **a**

#### **TECH SKILLS**

• HTML

· CSS

· SASS

PostCSS

Javascript

React

Vue

¡Query

Node

Webpack

· Gulp

Express

• Git

Wordpress

Photoshop

Illustrator

After Effects

MongoDB

Firebase

·SOL

Three

· GSAP

Bootstrap

Jest

# **ABOUT ME**

I'm a web developer from Woking, Surrey. I've been coding since 2016, primarily working with industry standard front-end technologies although I also have supplementary back-end experience.

I previously worked at a digital marketing agency in Guildford as the senior member of a small web team, before returning to my former job following redundancy. I've enjoyed the stability of this role throughout the uncertainty of the pandemic, while continuing to expand my technical skillset through personal projects and educational courses in preparation for the next step in my development career.

## **COURSES & CERTIFICATES**

MySQL: Real Database Experience

Udemy, 2022

**React For The Rest Of Us** 

Udemy, 2021

**Mastering The Modern Workflow** 

Udemy, 2020

**Vue.js & Firebase Web Apps** 

Udemy, 2020

**Full Stack Javascript** 

Udemy, 2020

**Wordpress Development** 

Udemy, 2019

**Online Marketing Fundamentals** 

Google Digital Garage, 2018

#### **UPCOMING COURSES**

Data Visualization With D3.js
Three.js Journey
Adobe Premiere Pro Essentials Training
Adobe Illustrator Advanced Training
Adobe Photoshop Advanced Training

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

Sainsburys

**General Assistant** 

July 2019 - present

**Delivered Social** 

Web Developer

August 2018 - June 2019

Sainsburys

Online Shopper

March 2016 - July 2018

Kemishford Painters & Decorators

**Administrative Assistant** 

July 2015 - July 2018

Sainsburys

**General Assistant** 

October 2011 - July 2015

## **EDUCATION**

A-Lv Mathematics (B)

A-Lv Psychology (C)

A-Lv Media Studies (C)

**AS-Lv Film Studies (C)** 

Farnborough Sixth Form College 2006-2008